少年变异忍者神龟
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
神龟报数
Turtles, count it off!
一 二 三 四
One, Two, Three, Four
忍者神龟 变异链式反应
Turtles! Mutant chain reaction
忍者神龟 生存在地下
Turtles! Livin' underground
忍者神龟 修练忍术
Turtles! Ninjitsu action
忍者神龟 在这个神奇的城市
Turtles! It's a shell of a town
神龟报数
Turtles, count it off!
一、恪守武术之道
One! Live by the code of the martial arts
二、人不犯我 我不犯人
Two! Never fight unless someone else starts
三、无论如何 生死与共
Three! Always stick together no matter what
四、若别无他法 该出手时就出手
Four! If all else fails, then it's time to kick butt
我爱当一只...
I love bein' a -
我爱当一只神龟
I love bein' a turtle
少年变异忍者神龟
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
神龟报数
Turtles, count it off!
一 二 三 四
One, Two, Three, Four
忍者神龟 无人能及
Turtles! There's no one better
忍者神龟 当心施莱德
Turtles! Watch out for Shredder
忍者神龟 他们独一无二
Turtles! They're like no others
忍者神龟 他们是好兄弟
Turtles! Those teenage brothers
一 二 三 四
One, Two, Three, Four
少年变异忍者神龟
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles